https://www.clearbags.com/privacy-policy/

Menu IndustriesCrafting & ScrapArt & Photo PackagingFood PackagingGeneral PackagingMedicinal PackagingFishingDirect Mail Wedding, Party & EventCollectibles PackagingHealthcare Solutions BagsCrystal Clear Bags ®Gusset BagsFood Safe BagsRetail BagsBags On a RollFlat Poly BagsHanging BagsClear Poly TubingZipper BagsEco Compostable BagsClear Door Knob BagsStatic Shielding BagsBarrier BagsRecord SleevesNewspaper BagsTropical Fish BagsChild Resistant BagsPrinted Warning BagsBoxesCrystal Clear Boxes ®Food Safe BoxesPillow BoxesPaper BoxesShipping BoxesWine BoxesTubesShoe Storage BoxesClamshell BoxesStationeryCrystal Clear SleevesCard Jackets and Slip CoversStationery BoxesEnvelopesCardsFrame CardsPaperInk Jet Photo PapersPackaging AccessoriesMats & BackingClearBags® Show KitsCrescent Pre-Cut MatsBacking BoardFoam BoardMounting AccessoriesSlip-In MatsSpecialtyCrystal Clear Photo MountsVinyl ProductsMedia SleevesSmartSleevesClear Slip-on Book CoversPhoto Booth SleevesDirect MailCD/DVD BagsGlassine Paper SheetsFacial ProtectionAccessoriesMounting TapesMounting CornersOrganza RibbonClear Hang TabsClear StickersMiscellaneous ItemsTwist Ties and Tin TiesStretch LoopsPre-Tied BowsTapeHeat SealersCookie BoardsSalesSale ItemsClearanceCustom Packaging
Account
Home
ClearBags Online Privacy Policy
ClearBags Online Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
; To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
; To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
; To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
; To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
; To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, We include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. You may also contact our Customer Service Department to remove, or adjust, email and/or settings.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to offer you more timely and accurate service.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by contacting our customer service representatives at 800.233.2630 or sales@clearbags.com.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.clearbags.com/faqs.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on 1/1/2020.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
© 2020 ClearBags. All Rights Reserved.
